https://www.thunderwolveshockey.com/page/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Thunderwolves Hockey respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this privacy policy. This privacy policy explains Thunderwolves Hockey Inc's treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on or related to this website ('Thunderwolves Hockey Website') and all services ('Thunderwolves Hockey Services') made available on this site. This privacy policy also explains how you can ask questions and make suggestions about our privacy practices and review and update your personal information.
We urge you to read this privacy policy carefully and to check back periodically as this privacy policy may change from time to time. Please note that this privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites, which are not owned or controlled by Thunderwolves Hockey.
Information Collected
In the course of operating the services, we may collect two types of information about our users: personal information and non-personal information.
Personal Information: is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, birth date and gender. personal information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when registering for a service, such as when you choose to subscribe to an Thunderwolves Hockey Service, enter an Thunderwolves Hockey promotion or choose to receive an Thunderwolves Hockey newsletter. In addition, if you choose to contact any of our customer service representatives, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter. We may also receive personal information from our business partners and other third parties, provided that such third parties confirm to us that you have permitted them to share such information.
Business contact information such as the name, title, business address, email address or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered personal information.
Non-personal Information: is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access an Thunderwolves Hockey Service, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors and average time spent on an Thunderwolves Hockey Service, is also considered non-personal information.
Non-personal information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating the Thunderwolves Hockey Services. For example, our Web servers may automatically collect non-personal information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie or through a Web Beacon when you choose to visit an Thunderwolves Hockey Service. Non-personal information is used by Thunderwolves Hockey as described here.
Use of Personal Information
Personal information may be used by us for the following purposes:
Providing you with the Thunderwolves Hockey Services and information you have requested from us, including your use of the Thunderwolves Hockey Site. We may from time to time use your personal information to contact you about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to the Thunderwolves Hockey Services;
If you indicated that you were interested in receiving offers or information from Thunderwolves Hockey Inc. or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, Thunderwolves Hockey or such sponsors or advertisers may send you email materials and other mailings about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. If at any time you would like to end your subscription to any such email materials, follow the directions posted at the bottom of the email material;
If you enter a contest or other promotion offered on Thunderwolves Hockey Website, we may, under the rules of the promotion, use your name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion;
Thunderwolves Hockey may also use personal information if it has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of a federal, provincial or foreign law or in order to protect or defend a legal interest.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. We will only disclose your personal information to third parties:
Where you have specifically given us your consent to disclose your personal information for a designated purpose;
Who are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers or service providers, solely to enable us to more efficiently provide you with the Thunderwolves Hockey. Such entities act under strict contractual controls, requiring them to maintain the confidentiality of all such personal information and to use such information solely for purposes related to the provision of the Thunderwolves Hockey Services;
As may be set out in the Terms of Use applicable to an Thunderwolves Hockey Service, to facilitate the provision of such Thunderwolves Hockey Service, such as fulfilling legal requirements;
As required by law, including by an order of any court, institution or body with jurisdiction or authority to compel the production of information, or in order to protect or defend a legal interest;
In connection with an Thunderwolves Hockey corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or a sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of Thunderwolves Hockey provided that the personal information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes permitted by this privacy policy by the entity acquiring the information.
Links to Other Sites and Advertisements
A Thunderwolves Hockey Service may contain links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This privacy policy applies only to the Thunderwolves Hockey Services referencing this privacy policy.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. Thunderwolves Hockey takes technical, contractual, administrative, and physical security steps to protect personal pnformation that you provide to us. We instruct our employees with access to your personal information that it is to be used only in adherence with the principles set forth in this privacy policy and the laws applicable to each specific business.
In certain areas, such as when you provide credit card information to us, we work to help protect the security of your credit card information during transmission by using industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology.
You can help protect the security of your personal information as well. For instance, never give out your password, since this is what is used to access your account or registration information. Also remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you finish using an Thunderwolves Hockey Service or surfing the web, so that other people using the same computer won't have access to your information.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Thunderwolves Hockey may from time to time change its privacy policy as new Thunderwolves Hockey Services are added or old ones changed. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted on Thunderwolves Hockey Website. Please check this privacy policy regularly for updates by checking the date of "Last Update" at the top of this document.
Additional Privacy Procedures
Privacy procedures specific to an Thunderwolves Hockey Service can be found on Thunderwolves Hockey Website at the location of the particular Thunderwolves Hockey Service. Those procedures are an addendum to this policy, and are provided to you at the place where they will be of most use and relevance to you.
Accessing and Changing Account/Registration Information
Thunderwolves Hockey provides you with the means to access, update, edit or delete any account or registration information you may have provided to us at any time on your own by going to the appropriate page in the account or registration section of the relevant Thunderwolves Hockey Service, and changing or deleting such information as desired.
If you are unsure whether we have a record containing any of your personal information and would like to confirm whether or not we do, please send an e-mail to our Privacy Manager at jtpayett@lakeheadu.ca, indicating all email addresses that you may have given us.
If you decide at any time that you do not want to receive any email materials to which you have subscribed, you may choose to unsubscribe to these e-mails by following the instructions at the bottom of the email material.
Questions, Comments or Suggestions
If you have questions, comments or suggestions about this privacy policy or Thunderwolves Hockey privacy practices that were not answered here, send our Privacy Manager an e-mail at jtpayett@lakeheadu.ca.
Information
Lakehead Thunderwolves
Varsity Hockey Corporation
Copyright © 2018
Court & Red
Pages
Team
News
Newsletter
Sign up to our newsletter and stay up to date with exciting information regarding the team.
The Lakehead University Thunderwolves Hockey Team is located in Thunder Bay, Ontario, Canada. It is made possible by the partnership of Lakehead University and the Lakehead Thunderwolves Varsity Hockey Corporation (a non-profit organization). Read Our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
Close
Home
Team
Coaches
Personnel
News
Schedule
Fan Zone
